This ain't no walk in the park.
Primitive War is a action, horror, war film directed by Luke Sparke.
During the Vietnam War, a recon unit ventures to an isolated jungle
valley to uncover the fate of a missing platoon.
They soon find themselves in a fight for their lives against
an unexpected enemy — prehistoric dinosaurs.
Colonel Jericho, played by Jeremy Piven.
Sofia, played by Tricia Helfer.
Baker, played by Ryan Kwanten.
Eli, played by Nick Wechsler.
Keyes, played by Anthony Ingruber.
Logan, played by Aaron Glenane.
Primitive War is a 2025 Australian science fiction action horror film directed by Luke Sparke and based on
the 2017 novel of the same name by Ethan Pettus, who both co-wrote the script for film.
Starring Ryan Kwanten, Tricia Helfer, Nick Wechsler and Jeremy Piven, the film is set in a Vietnam jungle valley during 1968 and follows a
reconnaissance unit who carries out a rescue mission for a US Army Special Forces platoon and are attacked by de-extinct dinosaurs.
A sequel is development, planned for a 2027 release.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, based on novel or
book, survival, prehistory, prehistoric creature.
The tone is dark.